Question 2
Where is Yasumori?
The answer is here!
Today, I'm going to play basketball!
Speaking of basketball, Yasumori is the
best!
Today, we have two people who are not
athletic.
Let's welcome them!
Welcome!
I'm back!
Just kidding.
We have two people who are bad at
sports.
I'm Yuna Basuke.
I'm Miyu Fujita.
How about you?
I'm not good at basketball.
When I was in elementary school,
I took a physical fitness test.
I got D.
D, C, C, C.
How about you?
I was in a class.
I was not good at it.
I know.
So, we are going to run.
Today,
we are going to play basketball
with two people who are bad at sports.
We are going to play basketball
with the hands of people who are not
good at sports.
Have you ever used the hands of people
who are not good at sports?
Let's play!
Go!
We are going to start with the physical
fitness test.
Go!
Do it like a basketball.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
You can do it!
I'm sure you can't score a goal.
The result is...
Yes!
Let's start with the basics of
dribbling.
I know how to dribble.
I know.
Let's go.
Let's try.
Ready, go.
I can't do it.
Wow.
I think you're doing well.
Watch yourself and remember the flick
from up above.
MI YA, your flick is a bit too high
there.
That's basic!
Now for the
It's good looking right?
I'll go next.
Please look at the camera.
I'll go.
I'm sorry.
Youkai is doing it.
Thank you for watching.
I can't do it!
But I can do the dribble if I can do
this.
So, it was a dribble.
I'll do this.
I'll do the dribble.
Next, I'll do the free throw.
Free throw?
Good!
I did it!
I can't stop today.
It's good.
It's like a Kunoji when you do the free
throw.
I did it!
Good!
It's difficult.
I'll do the three-point shot.
Follow me.
It was a Kunoji.
It was really Kunoji.
You stopped that part and did the free
throw.
It looked really good.
I'll ask you to edit it.
It looked good.
It was really cool.
The next one is a Kunoji.
Goes from over 30cm to his ultimate
height is 469cm
angle
10cm
Fall
It's dark
itals
Tokyo, because it's just right here…
Let's do the lay-up.
Thank you for the interview.
I'd be a
room.
Two
I
didn't
bring my
Can I have a refill?
Let's eat again.
Amazing!
Catch!
2!
Jump!
Wait!
It's my fault.
It's difficult.
I'm sorry to interrupt you.
Can you show me how to do it?
I'll show you.
I'll pass the ball.
Yes.
I'll pass the ball to the other team.
I'll run again.
Yuna will shoot.
I'll shoot.
I'll pass the ball to the other team.
Amazing!
The person on the left will shoot.
The person on the left?
I'll start.
Wait!
I'll run again.
I'll shoot.
I'll start.
I'll run again.
I'll shoot.
Don't stop!
Go, go, go!
Ready, go!
Go!
Run!
It's over!
To be continued
I've been practicing so far.
I'd like you to solve it together to
get the results.
I see.
I'm going to win if I win.
I'll have you do it one on one.
I'll send you a message of success with
rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
I won.
Yuka is the last one.
Yuna is the second.
I'll go.
Ready, go.
One.
Two.
Three.
I lost.
Wait a minute.
Four.
I lost.
You went too fast.
Can I do it?
Yes.
I'll send you a message of success.
Ready, go.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
I won.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
I'll send you a message of success.
Thank you for watching.
No, no, no.
It's in.
It's a diamond.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm not going to do it.
The winner is Yuna.
I couldn't keep up with Fujitani's
exercise.
I can't move as I want.
Let's shoot one last time.
Let's do it in a five-man formation.
1,2,3,4.
That's all.
We have a great punishment for Fujitani
who lost.
It's a massage stick.
There is a room with a massage stick.
Miyu, you will move to that room and
receive the punishment.
Let's go.
So,
As a result of the match between me and
Miyu,
Miyu lost 3 to 0,
so Miyu will receive a foot massage.
I thought it was this foot massage.
The one that walks.
Yes, the one that walks.
Then,
Today,
There seems to be a great foot massage
person.
May I call you?
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Please do it with a good feeling.
Then, let's go right away.
Excuse me.
Please.
I'm scared.
It's nothing.
Please relax.
Why?
I'm scared.
It's amazing.
It's nothing.
No.
I can do it.
What?
Really?
It feels good.
Why? I won.
Why?
I won because I couldn't take a
picture.
You are changing.
You are too much.
I won.
Wait a minute.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's pretty bad.
Wait!
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry.
What's wrong with it?
It's stomach.
I won.
How was it?
It's terrible.
I won.
Thank you.
Today, we played basketball
with two people
who are not good at sports.
As a result,
Fujitani Miyu is
at a disadvantage.
I'm disappointed.
I want to play with Tohoku-san next
time.
There are other people who are good at
sports.
Yes, there are.
We are not good at sports,
but we should practice.
We should play basketball with
the lifeguard.
We will play basketball
with other members
of the lifeguard.
It's impossible.
See you next week!
Bye!
Thank you!
I'm going to get angry.
I'm going to get angry because I'm
frustrated.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I'm dying! I'm dying!
What? What? What?
You are serious.
Wait! Wait!
You don't have to push so hard.
What is that?
Ouch!
I'm glad that you let me play a
punishment game.
I was surprised.
I played a punishment game.
I wanted to do it.
I will do it.
Please subscribe to our channel.